TOMÁS NAHUEL ANTELA RIZZO

JUNIOR FULLSTACK WEB DEVELOPER

CONTACT

+34 638653950

tomasnahuelantela@gmail.com

tomhuel.xyz

Tomhuel

Tomás Nahuel Antela Rizzo

SKILLS

Team Work

Iniciative

Motivated

Fluid learning

Effective Communication

Agiles Metodologies

RESIDENCE

Currently, I live in San Cristóbal de La Laguna, but I'm always willing to venture into new places, even if it means changing my usual place of residence.

I'm open to working remotely, in a hybrid setup, or in-person.

EDUCATION

Advanced specific vocational training in Web Development

IES Puerto de la Cruz

2021-2023

LANGUAGES

English Intermediate Spanish Native

ABOUT ME

Junior Full Stack Web Developer with experience on Laravel 8, Livewire, Javascript, etc. Interested in specialization on Backend, Python and IA's. Proactive and motivated to learn grow both personally and professionally.

I am interested in contributing and mutually benefiting with my colleagues and friends. Therefore, I am open to constructive proposals and opinions, aiming to generate a sense of comfort and trust in the people around me.Desarrollador

WORK EXPERIENCE

FullStack Developer

eAgora Algoritmo del Cambio

2023-2023

Period of training in Work Centers as FullStack Developer, focusing on Laravel 8 + Livewire + Bootstrap for Frontend development and Laravel Lumen + MySQL for Backend development.

Volunteer

Cerebritos_ 2017-2023

I have been volunteering with the Cerebritos_ association since I was 14 years old, participating in various activities such as being a monitor for different workshops in the field of multiple intelligences, a monitor and coordinator at the Gamer Forum of Los Realejos, and various activities related to team management and/or events.

TECHNOLOGIES

Languages

HTML 5 CSS 3

PHP

Git

MySQL

JavaScript

TypeScript

Java

Frameworks

Laravel Livewire Angular

Bootstrap 5

Interests

Python (IA's)

Backend (REST, GraphQL, ...)

Django & FastAPI